They won't know who we are
So we both can pretend
It's written on the mountains
A line that never ends
As the devil spoke we spilled out on the floor
And the pieces broke and the people wanted more
And the rugged wheel is turning another round
Dorian, carry on
Will you come along to the end
Will you ever let us carry on
Swaying like the children
Singled out for praise
The inside out on the open
With the straightest face
As the sad eyed woman spoke we missed our chance
The final dying joke caught in our hands
And the rugged wheel is turning another round
Dorian, carry on
Will you come along to the end
Will you ever let us carry on
Dorian, carry on
Will you come along to the end
Will you ever let us carry on
Dorian will you follow us down